

Contact

Phone 03312198808

Email codelink83@gmail.com

Address
Islamabad G11 (Willing to Relocate)

Skill

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap 5
- JavaScript
- REACT JS
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- Wordpress

Web Design

- Adobe Photo Shop
- Adobe illustrator
- UI UX Design Figma

Language

English

Urdu

Pashto

Muhammad ilyas </>

Web Developer

Welcome to my Profile I am Muhammad ilyas I have vast knowledge about 8 Months Experience in WEB , DEVELOPMENT (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap) & React js DESIGNING. I will develop a Professional website in latest version Also expertise in Data entry, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, Power point. Can handle complex problems in efficient way.

Experience

Web Developer 2022-2023 Certified from GTVC Tangi

Seeking an internship opportunity in a software house to apply and enhance my web development skills, particularly in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap JavaScript and MERN Stack. Excited to contribute to real-world projects, collaborate with industry professionals, and gain practical experience in a dynamic work environment.

November 2023 to 21 Feb 2024

Loin Software House Islamabad

Front end Developer Intern

- Developed a responsive website UI using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap 5, JavaScript and React js.
- Backend Node.js, Express.js, mongodb
- Customize and Update The client web site.
- Successfully debugged the web-related issues, leading to improved efficiency and performance.
- Analyzed user research trends and suggested changes to existing design processes for better results.
- Create a web app in React is as per experience only

Education

(FSC) FROM PESHAWAR BOARD

Six Months Diploma in web development (NAVTTAC)

GTVC (Tangi Mirzadhir) 2022 - 2023

My Goal

Achieve to Full Stack Developer